Guide to the New Dramatists Records
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Administrative Files, 1949-1996; Series II; 114.58; (100 boxes) + 12 broadside folders
  - Financial Records
    - Production Observance Meetings, 1959 April 2; 1 (Box 130, Item barcode 39002091245671)
    - Rigoletto, undated; 1 (Box 130, Item barcode 39002091245689)
    - Beethoven, undated; 1 (Box 130, Item barcode 39002091245697)
    - George [?]essel, undated; 1 (Box 130, Item barcode 39002091245705)
    - Manhatten Transfer Extensions, undated; 1 (Box 130, Item barcode 39002091245713)
    - "I Dare You to Persist Me", Pedro Juan Pietri, 1983 October 20; 1 (Box 130, Item barcode 39002091245630)
    - Masked Ball, undated; 1 (Box 130, Item barcode 39002091245721)
    - Reich / Debussy / Glass / Jolivet / Becker: Flute Pieces, undated; 1 (Box 130, Item barcode 39002091245739)
      Contents on this audiotape reel include:
      Vermont Counterpoint
      Syrinx
      Facades
      Asceses
      Stonehenge
    - Billy Joel / Vangelis / Diva / Phillip Glass, undated; 1 (Box 130)
      This audiotape reel contains commercial pieces. It has not been digitized.
    - Laura Cunningham, "Bang", 1984 April 9; 1 (Box 130, Item barcode 39002104617981)
      Contents of this audiotape reel are included below.
      Birds
      Crickets
      Hernando's Hideaway
      Rooster Crow
      Crickets / Birds
    - Talking Heads / Scott Johnson, undated; 1 (Box 130)
      This audiotape is commercial in nature. It has not been digitized.
    - William J. Sibley, "Mr. and Mrs. Coffee", 1986 February 12; 1 (Box 130, Item barcode 39002091245747)
    - Shostakovich, "Symphony #4", undated; 1 (Box 130, Item barcode 39002091245754)
    - Sherry Kramer, "End of Radio", undated; 1 (Box 130, Item barcode 39002091245762)
    - Romulus Linney, "Pops", 1986 January 16; 1 (Box 130, Item barcode 39002091245770)
    - David Hill, "In September Woods", 1985 October 30; 1 (Box 130, Item barcode 39002091245788)
    - Edie Cantor, "Collectibles", undated; 1 (Box 130, Item barcode 39002091245796)
    - Dick Zigun, "Red Letter Days", 1985 December 4; 1 (Box 130, Item barcode 39002091245804)
    - Masked Ball, undated; 1 (Box 130, Item barcode 39002091245812)
    - Tannhauser, undated; 1 (Box 130, Item barcode 39002091245820)
    - Faust, undated; 1 (Box 130, Item barcode 39002091245838)
    - Bill Sibley, "Define Success", 1984 March 30; 1 (Box 130, Item barcode 39002091245846)
    - "Calypso", undated; 1 (Box 130, Item barcode 39002091245861)
    - Dresser, "Better Days", 1986 April 17; 1 (Box 130, Item barcode 39002091245853)
    - Luncheon sign-in board, 1980 (Box 133(Broadside))
    - Luncheon sign-in board, 1984 (Box 134(Broadside))
    - Luncheon sign-in board, 1986 (Box 135 (Broadside))
    - Luncheon sign-in board, 1990 (Box 136 (Broadside))
    - Luncheon sign-in board, 1991 (Box 137 (Broadside))
    - Luncheon sign-in board, 1992 (Box 138 (Broadside))
    - Luncheon sign-in board, 1993 (Box 139 (Broadside))
    - Luncheon sign-in board, 1994 (Box 140 (Broadside))
    - Luncheon sign-in board, 1994 (Box 141 (Broadside))
    - Luncheon sign-in board, 1995 (Box 142 (Broadside))
    - Luncheon sign-in board, 1996 (Box 143 (Broadside))
    - Luncheon sign-in board, 1996 (Box 144 (Broadside))